sustainablebusiness.com 2013-07-30

# SustainableBusiness.com

Last Updated: December 2003

## SustainableBusiness.com is Committed to Protecting Your Privacy

We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets out our privacy policy and explains what we do with the personal information that we collect from our users.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact SustainableBusiness.com at info@sustainablebusiness.com.

We strive to offer our visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy.

## How we gather information from users.

SustainableBusiness.com collects a limited amount of information about our site visitors, so that we can provide a site that is interesting and useful, as well as provide advertising that is appropriate for our visitors. How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. You can visit many pages on our site without providing any information. Other pages may prompt you to provide information - your name, email address, and other personal information - when you register for access to portions of our site, sign up for our services, request certain features (e.g., newsletters, news updates and other products) or make a purchase. You may also provide information when you participate in contests, voting and polling activities, message boards and chat rooms and other interactive areas of our site.

If you use our email-to-a-friend service to email one of our articles to a friend or colleague, you will need to provide us with your friend's email address. We will automatically send this person a one-time email, sending them back to our web site to read the article. We will not use this email address for any other purpose.

Like most Web sites, we collect IP addresses to help us understand how our audience uses our site, so that we can improve our site and your experience while visiting SustainableBusiness.com. For this reason, if your browser is set up to accept them, we use a feature known as a "cookie." Cookies contain bits of information that Web sites transfer to your computer's hard drive for record keeping purposes. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. Cookies don't tell us who you are, however, only you can do that. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, but doing so may limit your ability to access certain portions of the site or may require you to re-enter your user name and password. And we may not be able to customize the site's features according to your preferences.

## What we do with the information we collect.

SustainableBusiness.com collects personal information to provide you with the best and most personalized Web experience possible and to provide our advertisers with an efficient means to reach the right audience.

We may ask you to register in order to use certain parts of our site. This will help us conduct research on our users' demographics and interests. We will use this information only on an aggregated basis. For example, you don't have to give us information, but we can't send you breaking news pertaining to solar unless you let us know you have this interest. We may need to contact you regarding changes in this Privacy Policy, to process e-commerce transactions or to tell you about services or products offered by our partners that you may find of interest. We may also use this information to contact you and ask for your feedback on one or more of our services.

We may aggregate information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive. Aggregated Information may be shared with our advertisers and business partners, but cannot be used to contact you individually.

We do not give, rent, lend, or sell individual information to our advertisers, only aggregate information. If we want to let you know about a partner offer, we will contact you, not our partner. We may also disclose aggregate information (for example, 50,000 readers clicked on a certain advertisement) to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.

When you place an order with SustainableBusiness.com, you need to give us the information necessary to process and fulfill your order, and notify you of your order status. We'll also notify you that your subscription has expired, if that is appropriate. If you pay for an order on-line the information is encrypted, using Secure Socket Layers (SSL) technology. If you prefer not to order on-line, you may also fax, mail or give us your order over the telephone. If you order on-line from one of the our partners', they will fulfill the order. They have their own privacy and data collection practices. SustainableBusiness.com does not have access to any personal information you may provide to our partners when making purchases from them.

If you use our email-to-a-friend service to email one of our articles to a friend or colleague, your email address will appear on the "From" line of this email, disclosing this information to whoever opens and reads the email.

We may also use this information for other purposes such as site administration and troubleshooting. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service and our newsletter provider, for example) may access such information.

As we develop our business further, we may sell, buy, or merge with other companies. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary to give such information to law enforcement authorities. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

The quality news and information on SustainableBusiness.com is partiallly supported by advertising revenue and a controlled program of e-mail marketing is an important element of our on-line publishing business. If you do not want to receive such offers and mailings, you can email us at info@sustainablebusiness.com and let us know. We'll remove your name from our lists immediately. Another way is to simply to click the unsubscribe link, which you will find on our email messages.

## Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements.

SustainableBusiness.com expects its partners, advertisers and third-party affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. However, third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to content that is created or hosted by a third party. You may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, advertisements, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. SustainableBusiness.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Through features available on our site, third parties may use cookies or other technology to gather information. SustainableBusiness.com does not control the use of this technology or the resulting information and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

The information you post on message boards and any other information exchange tools we may provide in the future is visible to the public. That's really the point of such tools. Please remember that whenever you disclose personal information publicly - for example, on message boards, through email, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information on-line that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

While we do our best to protect your personal information, SustainableBusiness.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. What does all this mean? Just as with anything else, you must protect yourself. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're on-line.

Certain areas of our sites are password-protected. Only you have access to these password-protected areas. We recommend that you do not share your passwords with anyone. SustainableBusiness.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. If you are using a computer that others have access to such as one in a computer lab, Internet cafe or public library, always remember to log out and close your browser window when leaving our site.

## Contacting us.

We can be reached by contacting:

SustainableBusiness.com  
231 West Pulaski Rd.  
Huntington Station, NY. 11746

Email: info@sustainablebusiness.com

## Changes to this policy.

SustainableBusiness.com may make changes to this Privacy Statement at any time, but we'll notify you of any substantive or material change (by way of email) and provide you with the opportunity to opt-out. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

In the event case of any conflict between the terms of this policy and the terms of any electronic or machine readable privacy policy (for example, a P3P electronic privacy policy), the terms of this written policy shall control.

|   
---|---
